(Penny:)I can't even believe this.
Maybe you should just go.
(Amy:)No, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I take it all back.
(Amy:)Look, I'm, uh... I'm sitting in your chair,
there's nothing wrong with it.
(Amy:)Please let me continue
to be part of your world.
(Sheldon:)Ow.
(Penny:)What's wrong?
Something in the chair is
biting my tushy. It's not importa... Ow.
Wait, wait, get up. Get up.
Swear you won't tell Sheldon!
(Amy(between screams):)I swear!
(Amy(between screams):)Can I tell my doctor?
I'm gonna need shots!
(Penny(also still screaming):)Yeah, sure!
(Leonard:)Oh, hey, babe.
I think I've figured this thing out.
- Oh, Leonard, listen...
- No, you listen.
(Leonard:)You're my woman and I'm gonna make
you feel things you've never feIt before.
(Scene:)- Leonard...
- That's right, say my name.